http://www.juliusblum.com/privacy-policy/

Drawing Files
Julius Blum & Co. Inc. product drawings are available in CAD (DXF and DWG) and PDF (Acrobat) formats. Select a format below to access the drawing files:
PDF DXF DWG
Julius Blum & Co., Inc. Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last modified on 12/15/2015.
Julius Blum & Co., Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates http://www.juliusblum.com/ (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We collect nonpublic personal information you provide to us when you request on catalog online or when you communicate with us using our contact form. The types of information we may collect include your name, address, phone number, email address and any other information you choose to provide.
Information Collection and Use
We may use your information, including nonpublic personal information as follows:
Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations;
Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
We take take reasonable measures to help protect all information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Additionally, we implement policies designed to protect the confidentiality and security of your nonpublic personal information. Julius Blum & Co., Inc. limits access to your nonpublic personal information to employees that have a business reason to know such information, and implements security practices and procedures designed to protect the confidentiality and security of such information and prohibit unlawful disclosure of such information in accordance with its policies.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to the homepages of our website or mobile application or by sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
Julius Blum product drawings are available in CAD (DXF and DWG) and PDF (Acrobat) formats. Select a format below to access the drawing files:
